梅德韦杰夫收获本赛季第三冠
Medvedev claims a third title of the season.
是的 这是一届很棒的比赛
Yeah, it was a great tournament.
很开心 很有意思
Fun, fun one.
也打了几场好球
Some good matches.
感觉自己打得不错
Felt some good tennis.
今天发球也很好
And today I served pretty well.
对此我很满意
So really happy about it.
能拿到冠军 真的很开心
And, yeah, happy, happy to get the title.
这对你来说也很有意义
And it's really something meaningful for you
和自己的同胞交手
to play against your compatriot.
你此前也曾
You had a previous experience
在决赛里和他交过手
of taking on him in a final.
而且赢下了那场比赛
And you won that one.
这次你也再次
And also you are the... you're the one
成为决赛的获胜者
who stands in this final.
这场决赛对你意味着什么？
So how does this final mean to you?
是的 我想说
Yeah, I mean,
这从来都不容易
it's never easy to play
和自己的同胞比赛
someone from your country.
总会比平时更在意一点
There is always a tiny bit more on the line.
虽然说到底 对手是谁并不重要
Even if, in the end, we don't care —
决赛无论对谁
whoever you play in the final,
你都想赢
you want to win.
但和同胞交手 还是更在意一些
But there's a tiny bit more on the line.
所以肯定会更紧张
So, for sure, a lot more nerves.
我觉得自己处理得不错
And I think I handled it well.
关键时刻 我打得很好
I played good in important moments.
我对自己的表现很满意
And I'm really happy about my level.
梅德韦杰夫又夺冠了
Medvedev, a champion
这是他夺冠的第23座不同城市
in a 23rd different city.
他的冠军履历多么丰富
What a portfolio this man possesses.
他是杭州最后的赢家
The last man standing in Hangzhou.